PROFILE SUMMARY

Experienced Police Officer with strong social science backgrounds including both political and legal aspects. Proven to have strong growth mindset and a grit to fail forward by stretching my learning capabilities to technology-related topics such as Python programming language. Seasoned in dealing with all types of stakeholders including those who are superior, inferior or peers to ensure quality work delivery.



Pol.Capt.Matra Jittanaphat

Email: matra.ov85@gmail.com Address: 19/191 Vibhavadi 60, Lak-si, 10210.

My Top 5 Clifton Strengths

- Ideation
- Restorative
- Context
- Self-Assurance
- Adaptability

Skills and Qualifications

- Police Airborne
- Marine Airborne
- Pressured Circumstances
 Handgun Defense 100/100
- Basis Python Programming
- Pacific Training Initiative (FRI)
- Open Water Diver (PADI)

Hobbies and Interest

- Listenine
- Teachin
- Reading
- Volunteering
- Basketball
- Rugby
- Shooting
- SHOOting
- Diving

Work Experiences

Royal Thai Police - Deputy Inspector, 2017 - Present

Staff of Deputy Prime Minister Gen. Prawit Wongsuwan, 2019 - Present

 Appointed by the Deputy Prime Minister to solve Land Ownership and Distribution issues in accordance with the Government Policy. My key achievements are as the following:

Reorganizing the Land Bank Administration Institute (Public Organization), 2019 - 2022

- Partnered with Ministry of Interior to spread the awareness of this newly established public organization in both online and offline realm to better help Thai citizens with land ownership and distribution matters
- Initiated a bottoms-up working system, which is very new for a governmental organization, to ensure that all
 citizens' voices are heard and addressed rather than working in a traditional top-down manner
- Created strong impact in more than 16 provinces in Thailand where we enabled local people to have legal
 rights to own lands and equipped them with the right skills and self-sufficient mindset to optimize lands
 utilization for themselves and future generations

Secretary to Pol.Gen.Chalermkiat Srivorakan, Deputy Commissioner-General, 2017 - Present

 Appointed by the Deputy Commissioner to coordinate crime suppressions regarding narcotics and natural resources and environment crime. My key accomplishments are as the following:

Drug Abuse Resistance Education Program (D.A.R.E), 2017 - 2019

- Initiated the D.A.R.E program to train our police officers with LAPD in an one-on-one circumstance to reinforce knowledge, skills and attitude related to drug abuse resistance
- Successfully trained more than 3,700 police officers to complete the program before deploying them to
 pass on their calibers directly to students and teachers nation-wide, educating more than 300,000
 individuals within the first year of the program

Illegal Logging Suppression Initiative, 2017 - 2018

- Investigated and arrested more than 2,600 individuals who were illegally logging natural resources in the North Eastern provinces of Thailand within two years
- Confiscated criminals' assets with a value of more than THB 100,000,000

Police I-Lert-U Application Initiative, 2017 - 2019

- Initiated a revolutionized method to call the police for help by proposing a one-stop and easy-to-use application for citizens to use instead of being stuck in a call-only system
- Included 1,482 police stations nation-wide to be a part of the application in order to provide real-time supports to citizens across the country
- Launched the application for public use and gained more than 1,500,000 downloads on Appstore and 500,000 downloads on Play store and had an average of 300 user requests per day. The application is proven to be the most downloaded and effective applications ever launched by the Royal Thai Police

Education Background

Chulalongkorn University: Bachelor of Arts, Political Science: Government (2013 – 2016)

- Vice President of Public Relations Department, Chulalongkorn University Student Government
- Chulalongkorn Rugby Team's Captain leading the team to secure Championship Trophy in both National and University Level
- Vice President of Chulalongkorn University International Forum gathering hundreds students from around the globe to address major global issues

Sripatum University: Bachelor of Laws (2018 - 2020)

Chulalongkorn University: Master of Public Administration (2020 - Present)